alorica.com 2008-06-16

# Alorica - Privacy Policy

Alorica Inc.® is committed to protecting our customer's privacy. We believe in providing an environment for our customers to have a sense of security in dealing with Alorica Inc.®. The information that a customer provides for using our services and for inquiries and submissions is held in our safe servers in order to maintain and ensure the customer's privacy. Should you have any issues, concerns, or comments please feel free to let us know. You may contact us at: [marketing@alorica.com](mailto:marketing@alorica.com). 

**What Information Is Being Collected**  
The amount of information we collect depends on the customer. We collect the information in order to provide a better, more efficient experience for you as well as for secure use of our services. There are two types of information that we collect, non-personal information and personal information. In general, you can browse our Website without giving us any personal information 

**Non-Personal Information**  
We automatically track and collect information when you visit our Website including but not limited to: 

  1. **Your IP address.** We use your IP addresses to measure our Website traffic and to improve your experience on our Website. The collection of IP addresses is used for the purpose of system administration, to gather broad demographic data, to enable ads to be served on our Website, to report non-personal information to our advertisers, and to monitor the level of activity on our Website. 
  2. **Browser type.** This information is captured to help optimize the customers' experience with us to match the latest technology used by our customers. 
  3. **Movements through our Website**. We will keep track of pages you visit to help improve your experience on our Website. 

**Personal Information**  
In order for you to utilize our services, we may require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you. Information may include: 

  1. **Contact data** (such as your name, mailing and e-mail addresses)
  2. **Financial data** (such as your account or credit card number)
  3. **Demographic data** (such as your zip code). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms or surveys, any information provided in such communication may be collected as personal information. This information is collected in order to provide you with our services, to communicate with you about the services that you ordered and to inform you of any new promotions or services. 

**Use Of Personal Information**  
We may use contact data to send you information about our company, our products, our services, or promotional material from some of our partners. We may also use this information to contact you about the products or services that you have ordered. We may use your financial data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for products or services. We use your demographic data to customize and tailor your experience on our Website by displaying content that we think might be interesting to you according to your preferences. We may also use your information to alert you to any special offers or other new products and services that become available in a newsletter or advertisement. 

**Cookies**  
There are various technologies, including one called "cookies", which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Website. A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some of our Website pages use cookies or other technologies so that we can better serve you when you return to our Website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Cookies may also be placed when you link to another Website not controlled by us or by independent third parties who actually operate the servers in which an advertisement resides. Although we may encourage third parties to adhere to appropriate privacy standards and policies, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of such parties. 

**Information Disclosure**  
Due to existing regulations and requirements, we cannot guarantee that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways other than described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or to a court of law, to third parties to comply with a court order or other legal process, to protect our rights or property, to enforce the Terms & Conditions of this Website, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we use industry leading practices (explained in more detail below) to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

Your personal information is not shared or sold with any other party. However, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**How Do We Protect your Information?**  
We stay on the leading edge of today's technology when it comes to protecting your personal information. We employ powerful 128-bit encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers (SSL) in all areas where your personal identity is required. For your protection, we are certified by VeriSign. Access to the customer's personal information is restricted within our company to authorized sales, customer service and accounting personnel to provide maximum security. 

**Who May See The Customer's Personal And Account Information?**  
Only authorized sales, customer service and accounting personnel of our staff may see the personal information of our customers. No other personnel are allowed or have access to this information. Those authorized sales, customer service and accounting personnel that have access to the personal and account information of our customers are required to keep the information confidential and may not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Alorica Inc. 

**How Do Customers Correct Or Update Personal Information?**   
We want you to have the ability to access and edit the personal information that you give us. During the process of online ordering you can review, change, or delete the information you submit to us. You can also update your basic account information at any time by email or by phone. We encourage you to update your information if it changes. Should you ask to have the information on your account removed or deleted, we will not be able to do so completely because we keep track of past purchases and will not be able to delete information pertaining to such past purchases. Also, we back-up the data stored on our systems as a security measure and such information cannot be completely deleted from our database. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases. 

**Public Forums**  
This Website may offer chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We may, but are not obligated to, monitor and review such chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups and we reserve the right to remove, in our sole discretion, any information, data, text, images, messages and other materials ("Content") deemed to be offensive, abusive, indecent, defamatory, obscene or otherwise inappropriate. 

**Content and Member Conduct**  
You are solely responsible for the Content you publish or display (hereinafter, "post") on our chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. You understand that all Content, whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated. This means that you, and not Alorica Inc.® or any of its affiliates, are entirely responsible for all Content that you upload, post, transmit or otherwise make available via our chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. We do not control the Content posted via our chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups and, as such, do not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such Content. You understand that by using our chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups, you may be exposed to Content that offensive, abusive, indecent, defamatory, obscene or otherwise inappropriate. Under no circumstances will we or any of our affiliates be liable in any way for any Content, including, but not limited to, for any errors or omissions in any Content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, emailed, transmitted or otherwise made available via our chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. 

**Opting Out Of The Newsletter And Advertisements**  
We may use your information from time to time to alert you of special offers, promotions, or services that become available in a newsletter or advertisement. If you would like to opt-out or stop receiving our newsletter and/or advertisements, you may follow the instructions in the email or contact us by phone or email and we will promptly remove you from our mailing list. 

**Links To Advertisers and Other Websites**   
Our Website contains links to other Websites. Alorica Inc.® is not responsible for the privacy practices or the Content of such advertisers or Websites. We may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you from a third party link. Please understand that any information that is disclosed by you directly or indirectly through a link or click-through in these areas becomes public information that is not controlled by us. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information through links or click-throughs. Web links are provided as a convenience and the inclusion of such Web links does not imply any endorsement of the associated Website or its Content by Alorica Inc.®. You understand that and agree that use of any Content contained on a third party Website is done at your own risk. 

**Updates and Changes To This Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to amend, modify, update, change or add to this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice by posting such amendments, modifications, updates, changes or additions on our Website. All such amendments, modifications, updates, changes or additions will automatically go into effect after posting on our Website. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to ensure that you are aware of any such amendments, modifications, updates, changes or additional terms to which you are bound. 

Copyright © 1998 - 120  Alorica Inc.® All Rights Reserved
